Space, the final
frontier, is a
vast and
mysterious
universe that has
captivated human
imagination for
centuries. Did
you know that the
universe is
estimated to be
around 13.8
billion years
old? It's a
mind-boggling
number that puts
our existence
into
perspective. The
International
Space Station
orbits the Earth
at an altitude of
around 250 miles,
completing one
rotation every 90
minutes. Space
exploration has
led to numerous
breakthroughs,
including the
discovery of
exoplanets,
which are planets
that orbit stars
outside our solar
system. Over
4,000 exoplanets
have been
discovered so
far, and the
number is growing
rapidly. Black
holes on the other
hand are regions
of space where
gravity is so
strong that
nothing, not even
light, can
escape. As we
continue to
explore space,
we're constantly
reminded of how
small we are in the
grand scheme of
things. Yet it's
this curiosity
and drive to
explore that will
ultimately
propel us forward
into the unknown.